Perfect, right? So you see the difference, right? You feel the difference, actually. Here,
feels more of a scientific kind of space, you know? And this tool is way more of a pro tool when
it comes to doing deep researches and doing serious researches as you see. So as you saw, it just
started explaining. It didn't say hello. It did not at all try to become my friend or anything like that,
you know? So other air tools are like that, right? So they are conversation-based AI tools.
Well, this one is actually focused on getting data and getting the most accurate data
as accurate as possible, you know? And we also have 10 resources over here for this small
piece of text, right? So if I click here, you'll see that we are able to check where this information
comes from, where exactly, right? So we have all these links. So perplexity is perfect,
you know? When it comes to its own use case and its own usage, it's actually perfect
about learning, about fact checking, you know? And all those stuff,